(Hankuk University)
This isn't it either.
Excuse me.
Are you a student of this school?
Yes, why do you ask?
I was transferring credits to major in
applied music this semester.
Could you tell me where
the Arts and Culture Department
building is?
Oh, yes, just follow me.
Looks like you're having a hard time.
Here's the Arts and Culture Department.
Thank you.
What? Where did he go?
"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 1: Repetition of coincidence is destiny!)
(Library)
Ah... Who put this there?
That student from before.
(The next day)
Oh. You're here again.
We meet again.
The exam is coming up soon.
I'm not the type to really study,
but I still have to take the exam.
Ah, I see.
You can apply through the school app.
Ah, the app.
I'm more of an analog person.
Ah, I see.
Please show me your student ID.
Well... I didn't bring my student ID.
What? Why are you laughing?
Then please tell me your name.
You know your student number, right?
Of course! My name is Yoon Chan.
A one-syllable name?
Yes. Yoon Chan.
Everyone calls me 'Chan'.
(Yoon Chan)
- And your student number?
- My student number is 22016934.
The Taekwondo Department.
Are you in the Taekwondo Department?
Yes.
Umm...
Before you transferred to
the Cultural Arts Department,
what was your major?
Huh? Why?
Oh, it's nothing...
Last time you said
you transferred credits here,
so I thought we might be
in the same year.
Well, you know...
I thought it'd be nice to get to know
each other if we're the same age.
Do you always laugh that loudly?
Huh?
Since we're in the library,
could you lower your voice a bit?
Yes, you can take the books now.
Ah, okay.
I'm quite a good person, you know?
There's nothing to lose by
becoming friends, right?
Wait.
He'll probably return and take it.
How many times do you have to lose it
to write your name on your wallet?
I'd better go home.
He's really weird.
We won't meet again, right?
He's not the type to
come to the library.
I'm so hungry.
What should I eat?
Hey! What?
Why do you keep appearing?
Ugh... Creepy.
Strange. Am I seeing things?
This kid, why are you that surprised?
Are you unwell?
No, Professor.
I'm fine.
Oh. Let's introduce ourselves.
This is a new student in Applied Music,
Jeong Woo Hyuk.
And this is a senior in Applied Music,
Kim Min Jae.
Hello, senior!
I'm Jeong Woo Hyuk.
Hello. I'm Kim Min Jae.
Senior, feel free to speak casually.
Oh, yes. Take your time...
Is working in the library okay?
- Yes, it's fun.
- Really?
Thanks to you, I got a scholarship
while I get to work.
Thank you so much.
Working in the library,
collecting credits for your major,
isn't it hard?
Don't skip meals because you're busy.
Make sure you eat regularly.
Yes, Professor.
As you advised, I always make sure
to eat properly.
Really?
- But, Professor,
- Yes?
Is that student a repeater
or a transfer student?
No. Does he seems like it?
Yes, he seems much older than me.
No, he's a 19-year-old freshman.
Really?
That aside,
are you adapting to school?
Yes, a little.
The school is quite big,
so I haven't explored everything yet.
Really? Is there anyone bothering you?
But everyone's an adult, I guess not.
No, who would bother me?
And if they do,
I'm not the type to just sit still.
Alright then.
If you ever need counseling,
you know my door is always open, right?
Yes, Professor.
And it'd be good if
you could help Woo Hyuk out.
He's in a similar situation as you.
Get along well and help each other.
Yes.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry, did I startle you?
We meet quite often, don't we?
They say repeated encounters
are pre-determined,
does that mean we're fated to be together?
Meeting this frequently means
our souls are compatible,
shall we be friends?
To be friends,
you have to start talking, right?
Okay?
Hmm, tasty.
What are you doing...
You don't have anyone to eat with?
Since we decided to be friends,
if you don't have anyone to eat with,
call me.
You see, I...
will make a good meal companion.
Who is this guy?
Since we're friends,
I'll give you a university tour anytime,
There's no place in the university
where I haven't been to.
He's really a strange guy.
Wake up, Kim Min Jae.
Your snacks are delicious.
It's not a snack, it's my lunch.
But I feel like I forgot something.
It feels a bit strange.
Ah, I don't know, I'll remember later.
I often forget and lose things.
Oh!
Your eyes
sparkle like the bus stop
in front of the university.
What?
Are my eyes like the bus stop?
Why?
I thought the lights on the bus stop
in front of the university were pretty.
Oh! I remember now.
Next time, I'll repay you
with something tastier.
I know a sandwich shop
that's even tastier.
Do as you like.
So, we'll see each other again?
So, we're actually friends, right?
Huh? Wait.
Seeing each other a few times
already makes us friends?
Oh, right, your wallet!
- You left your wallet.
- Oh!
I'm late, haa...
I'm late for the workout meet-up.
See you again, friend.
Haa...
As expected.
Strange.
Really strange.
Hello.
I'm Kim Min Jae, a librarian.
Do you know that you lost your wallet?
It's at the library, come and get it.
His name is Kim Min Jae.
Even his name sounds cool.
Welcome.
We could've just met it at the library,
why come to the cafe?
Because I'm grateful.
I wanted to buy something tasty for you.
The cake here is really delicious.
But I don't have much time to stay here.
Ah, you're using polite speech again.
Where are you going again?
I'm not a person who gets along easily
with anyone like you.
And I have to go work part-time.
We get along since we're the same age.
What's so hard about it?
Excuse me.
Your coffee and strawberry sandwich
are here.
Enjoy your meal.
Here. Ahh...
- Wait, I'll eat by myself.
- Oh!
You're not using polite speech.
See! It's not that hard.
Come on.
Ahhh...
Umm...
Did you know you lost your wallet?
I'm just so used to losing things.
You're an athlete
but you're good at eating.
I exercise as much as I eat.
Ah. Should I teach you how to work out?
I don't have time for that.
And I'm not cut out for exercise.
So, I'll just show you.
I'm not really interested in exercising.
If you learn from me,
you might become interested.
I'll adjust the schedule.
Well, do as you like.
So, we'll see each other again?
So, we're really friends, right?
By the way...
Is it normal for you to become
close with just anyone?
I don't have many friends.
But I really want to
become close with you.
You...
Do you have a lot of friends?
Not really...
I'm just always working part-time.
Perfect!
We can see each other every day.
Every day?
I'm not that free.
I'll just come to the library.
A library isn't a place to hang out.
I'll go there to see you.
What's with suddenly
making friends like this?
Are you hungry?
I'll take you somewhere nice.
I owe you for eating
your sandwich last time.
It's okay, you don't have
to pay me back.
Just let me pay back. Okay?
Please don’t' refuse, let's go together.
Okay? Okay?
Yeah.
Let's go.
(Cafe "Bokeh" is hiring
part-timers, flexible hours.)
They're hiring part-timers?
Min Jae.
Why aren't you coming?
Ah, I'm coming.
(Cafe "Bokeh" is hiring
part-timers, flexible hours.)
What a strange person.
Didn't we see each other several times?
Why the informal speech?
He's always asking to be friends.
I can't get used to it.
Ah, right.
I need to call the cafe owner.
Hello?
- Yes, hello, boss.
- Yes?
I'm the student who visited
the cafe around 6 p.m. earlier.
Ah,
the university student
who came with a friend, right?
Friend?
Ah, yes, that's right.
Actually,
I saw the job posting for
a part-time position at the cafe,
- Yes?
- I really want to do that job,
so I was wondering if
it would be okay for me to have
an interview for the job.
An interview? It's our pleasure.
How about this Wednesday at 7 p.m.?
Yes, thank you.
Then I'll see you on that day.
- Yes.
- Yes! Thank you, boss!
Yes!
I need to make money!
Yay!
I'll pass the job interview, right?
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Everyone,
I am a professor of Applied Music
at Hankuk University.
Now,
are you ready to embark on a journey
towards a deeper world?
Abandon the academic world
and come gain new knowledge
and experiences with me
in a world that is deeper
and broader than before.
I will wait for everyone.
Please follow and support 'Blossom Campus'
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
I love you.