(Library)
Hello, friend.
Yes?
Again.
Why so formal? We're friends.
Hey.
We're friends.
Friends.
Yeah.
Greet me.
Hello.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a book on
harmonic theory.
Could you help me find it?
Sure, just a moment.
- Yes.
- Hey, you.
Yes?
Shouldn't we follow the order?
Oh, order?
I've been watching
from behind for a while,
it doesn't seem like you
came to borrow a book.
I'm really here to borrow a book.
Stop! Stop!
Hey, gentlemen.
This is a library.
If you're here to borrow books,
please wait quietly,
If you're here to fight, please leave.
Check Zone 12-1.
Yes.
Senior, when are you going to help me
- with my guitar practice?
- Hmm, soon.
But first, find your book.
Yes.
Come in.
"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 2: Can We Become Friends?)
When will this busy period end?
Huh?
I have to finish this by today.
Stop talking.
Fine.
But buy me tteokbokki.
You talk too much.
You know that, right?
I do.
You're aware but you still
bother me all day?
What? When did I bother you?
And besides,
we're friends, can't we chat?
I'm feeling bad now.
Oh, you're feeling bad?
But your friend is working hard.
And you're not even helping, huh?
Aren't you hungry?
How about instant noodles?
I want to eat fried food
in front of the university too.
How many words do you say in a day?
I'm busy right now.
- Let's go.
- No.
Huh? Let's go.
I said no.
Come on, I'll treat you.
Let's go, it's my treat.
I said no.
Please, I can't eat alone.
No.
I'll teach you, listen.
This is how it's done.
No, I did it properly earlier.
You asking for it?
Hey, Yoon Chan.
Why are you in there?
Uh... Well...
I'm here to borrow a book.
Yeah,
so why are you sitting on that side?
Oh...
Umm... He's my friend.
My friend.
Oh.
I requested to return it
through the app.
Yes.
It's done.
But are you two really friends?
Why?
Oh,
this guy doesn't have any friends,
it's the first time
I've seen him with someone.
Yes, we're friends.
I'm off.
Yes.
I said no.
Please, I can't eat alone.
- No.
- Let's go eat together.
Boo!
Be quiet.
Okay, I'll do it.
No need.
I said no need.
No need to help me.
What are you doing?
I said no.
- Stop it.
- I don't want to.
The more you stop me, I more I want to.
What are you doing?
I said stop it.
Sorry.
See?
It's nice to have a tall friend, right?
Is it good or not?
Huh?
You're going to drop the book.
Why do you dislike expressing yourself
when you're happy?
By the way, do you
really have no friends?
I don't have any friends?
You're here!
No, not me.
Apart from me, is there anyone else?
Umm...
Yes.
Don't you think that's strange?
How can you have only one friend?
Yeah.
But is that weird?
You don't have any friends either.
I'm your only friend.
No, I intentionally don't make friends.
Umm...
I...
Just need one friend.
A real friend.
Don't do it.
I said don't do it.
Why?
Why did you hide?
Yeah. Why did we hide?
What?
Can't your junior
see us together?
How could we do that?
Never mind.
I have to work. Off you go.
Now!
(Private practice room)
You keep surprising people,
that's why you don't have any friends.
I told you I'm satisfied
with just one friend.
But why did you come all the way here
instead of going to the practice room?
It's a bit uncomfortable.
Yeah, the practice room was a bit small.
No.
That's not the reason.
It's uncomfortable and
things don't work out.
I thought getting some
fresh air might help.
Min Jae.
- Get up and come here.
- Why?
There's a better place for you
to practice guitar.
Let's go.
Min Jae, this way.
Isn't it nice?
This is the best view from our school.
Yeah.
It's nice indeed.
The atmosphere is great.
Can I request a song?
Mr. Composer?
No.
Just one song.
Huh?
Alright.
Why are you like that?
Huh?
What?
Are you crying?
That's crazy.
Who's crying?
It's just touching.
It's like respect for art.
You're obviously crying.
Senior!
What are you doing here?
Guitar!
Practicing guitar.
But how did you know
about this place, Senior?
This is my practice hideout.
But Senior, you're too much.
You said you'd practice
guitar with me...
Ah, sorry.
Let's practice together next time.
I'll do it more often.
Umm... Woo Hyuk.
I have something serious to
discuss with this guy right now, so...
Ah,
you want me to leave.
Alright.
What was that just now?
Ah!
It's great to have a friend.
It's great.
Hey!
What was that kiss earlier about?
Min Jae!
Come quickly.
- Come quickly.
- I don't understand.
Why did I feel that way?
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Hello.
I'm the youngest, Jeong Woo Hyuk.
The youngest and
the junior of Senior Min Jae.
What?
You don't believe that I'm the youngest?
But I am the youngest.
With a surprising charm
different from my appearance,
I'll captivate
Senior Min Jae and you guys.
Look forward to it.
Please love 'Blossom Campus' a lot.
Next, let me ask a question.
Oh, let me have some.
- Would you like some?
- Yes.
- Hmm?
- Mmm.
Is it tasty?
He was glaring at me earlier.
Scary.
Hmm, it's tasty!
It tastes better when someone feeds us.
It's an honor.
Wow. Fun.
Yeah.
It's so much fun.
Huh?
By any chance, are you
Yoon Chan and Min Jae from the drama?
Yes, that's us.
So nice to meet you.
May I shake hands with you?
Thank you, thank you.
What an amazing coincidence.
To watch "Blossom Campus"
in the same theater.
There are so many seats,
we ended up sitting together.
What an incredible coincidence.
Since we've met like this,
could we talk briefly about the drama?
Oh. Yes.
Thank you.
Could you briefly introduce your roles?
I'm Son Byeong Hoon,
I play Kim Min Jae's role,
Min Jae grew up in a poor environment
because he doesn't want to
seem pitiful to others,
he tries to act tough all by himself.
And he likes to act cold to others,
but he gradually warms up to Yoon Chan.
That's Min Jae's personality.
I'm Choi Dong Ho,
I play Yoon Chan's role.
Yoon Chan is lively
and has a quirky image.
He doesn't care much about others.
He only expresses his feelings
a lot to Min Jae.
I think fans would also be interested
in the actors themselves.
Min Jae and my personality
seem similar in some ways,
and not in other ways.
Compared to Yoon Chan's character,
I'm quite the opposite.
Yoon Chan is high-energy and lively,
while I'm not like that.
Really?
But I don't think the you I know
is like that.
Are there interesting or
memorable moments
from the filming so far?
Before going into standby,
I'd play jokes on purpose
to boost my energy.
It was fun when Min Jae
responded to my jokes.
- For example?
- For example,
I can't dance at all,
but I know just one move,
You know 'Super Shy' song?
When I do cute move like this,
Min Jae would do the rest of the moves.
Please show us.
- Please dance for us.
- You show it.
- What?
I already did it.
During the filming of this drama,
did you encounter any challenges
for the first time?
This is my first time doing this kind of acting,
although I've done other acting before.
In the past, I have played
hot-tempered roles
or villain roles.
But Yoon Chan's character
is very bright and lively,
I was a bit afraid and a little worried,
but Min Jae helped me through it.
As for me, I've only played
bright and lively roles,
a total opposite.
Compared to characters
I've played before,
Min Jae is quite colder.
It was refreshing.
During the filming,
how does the relationship between.
Min Jae and Yoon Chan unfold?
At first, it's like,
"Oh, this person exists."
It's not bad, that's how I feel.
But now, I'm trying to
appeal to Min Jae,
so I'm trying to establish my presence.
Min Jae has been curious about Yoon Chan
since they first met.
He didn't know what
emotion it was at first,
then he'll realize in
the second half of the story.
So in their relationship,
is there a part that
fans can look forward to?
Yoon Chan is
very aggressive.
- I'm too embarrassed to say.
- And Min Jae is...
- also aggressive as well.
- Right, right.
So it's like, "Look at them".
That kind of feeling.
The audience can look forward to
the latter part of the story.
Through filming this drama, what kind of
growth do both of you expect as actors?
Since this is my first shoot for
a this kind of show,
I might experience a lot of growth
because I have no experience on set.
As I accumulate experience,
in the future, I might become more
comfortable entering a scene.
Since it's my first lead role
in a drama,
I want to show a lot of acting skills
to the audience.
Is it progressing as you expected?
I'll work hard.
Then finally,
please tell us why we must
watch this drama.
"Blossom Campus"
I'm in it, so you have to watch it.
Hey! I was gonna say that!
Are you taking a test now?
No.
Because a handsome person is in it,
you have to watch it.
Our drama is a flower garden.
Thank you for talking with me today.
Oh, no problem.
I hope we will have
the opportunity to meet again.
- Especially at the theater.
- Oh! Sure.
You can leave first,
I'll sit here and enjoy the theater
for a bit before leaving.
It's over.
I need to feel this atmosphere.
You can leave first if you want.
- Thank you.
- See you later.
- Yes.
- Goodbye.
Let's go.