What was that just now?
Ah!
It's great to have a friend.
It's great.
Hey!
What was that kiss earlier about?
(Min Jae, do you want to
have dinner together?)
(Min Jae, what are you doing?
Let's hang out)
(Min Jae, today's lunch is bulgogi!)
"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 3: I Keep Wanting to See You)
Are you very busy?
Oh! Professor.
It's been a while since we met,
can we have a chat?
Can we go talk somewhere else?
Ah... But it's about to get busy soon.
Min Jae!
Oh!
Hello, Professor.
- Who is this?
- I'm Min Jae's friend.
From the Taekwondo department.
Ah,
I heard that Min Jae made a friend,
so it's you.
Min Jae has told me a lot about you.
Really? He didn't bad-mouth me, did he?
Geez, Professor...
You...
Can you cover for Min Jae for a bit?
It won't take long.
I just want to have a chat
with Min Jae outside for a bit.
Yes, don't worry.
Can you handle it?
Of course!
I've been watching you do it every day.
Handling your studies
and working at the library,
isn't it hard?
The schedule is tight,
but it's manageable.
Really?
Regardless, I'm grateful that
you've adapted so quickly.
At the beginning of the transfer,
you applied for counseling almost
every other day.
But after you've been busy,
we hardly met each other.
Was I like that?
Exactly.
It was nice to have someone to talk to.
But now, there's no one to talk to.
Professor.
Yes?
How about I apply for
counseling again?
You little rascal.
You don't have to force yourself to make up
a story for counseling.
It's a real counseling session.
Oh, really?
Then, let's hear it.
Ah... You see...
We're definitely a friend...
Well...
Umm...
You're friends and?
Ah,
I don't know if it's right to have
these feelings for a friend.
What kind of feelings?
Well...
Logically, it seems wrong,
but my heart keeps
circling back to that person.
Really?
Does that mean...
you love this friend?
I'm not sure yet.
This is my first time feeling this way,
so I'm not sure if it's okay.
I've felt the same way before.
You did, Professor?
Yes.
Ummm...
In middle school,
around second year?
An older female cousin from Seoul
came to my hometown
to travel and rest up.
After school,
I would go to her and study.
It gave me a passion for studying,
Haa...
And that gave me a dream
of going to Seoul to study.
Mmm...
Huh?
Professor, aren't you from Seoul?
Right?
I appear like a local from Seoul.
Actually, my hometown is Miryang.
Now that you mention it,
I remember you saying
you had a tough time in Seoul.
Ah...
I came up to Seoul only for studying,
and from high school admission
to college graduation,
it was really tough.
You really went
through a lot, Professor.
So,
what happened to
your older female cousin?
Ah, right.
How did we end up with
you comforting me?
Haa...
The more time I spent with her,
the stranger my feelings became.
I kept
missing her,
thinking about her constantly,
wanting to be with her,
but at the same time,
wondering if it was okay since
she was my cousin.
It was tough.
So, you loved your own cousin?
Hmm...
Love?
So, do you love that person
like that too?
Geez, what love?
What's with the surprise?
Is love a crime?
Yes. That's true.
Yeah, love itself isn't the issue.
But I'm not sure what my feelings
for that friend truly are.
Hmm... I felt the same way.
Back then,
I didn't even know
what those feelings were.
It took a long time for me
to understand them.
Time...
So, it took a lot of time.
In order to be sure of your feelings,
it takes a lot of time.
Of course,
everyone feels it at different paces,
so,
don't be too impatient.
There's no need to rush.
Yes.
Have a bit more trust
in yourself.
You're quite a good guy.
You can trust yourself.
Thank you, Professor.
Thanks to you, I feel like
I've understood something today.
Professor,
loving your cousin,
it wasn't wrong either.
I said that's correct.
No, click this and scroll down.
How can this be correct?
I said it's correct.
Ugh, I'm speechless.
- Dammit...
- No.
- Give it here.
- What?
- I'll do it.
- Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Min Jae!
You see,
I'm doing my job,
and he keeps interfering!
Interfering?
Because he's clumsy,
people were getting behind,
everyone was in a rush.
I thought it would turn
into chaos if I didn't help.
What?
I was just a bit slow.
Just a little slow, you know?
He just made things worse
by interfering.
Senior.
Why do you trust someone like him
to manage the library?
If you knew he almost destroyed
the library computer...
You'd have freaked out, wouldn't you?
No, I'm doing the right thing.
- Pull it up.
- I said no, that's not it.
Hey, gentlemen.
This is a library.
Please go outside and fight.
Why the formal language again...
Get out quickly.
Get out quickly!
Hurry.
- Go.
- But I...
Ugh, seriously.
(Library)
Anyway...
I understand that you were
trying to help,
I'm sorry for snapping at you.
Ah, yeah.
I'll be off then.
Please wait.
Back then...
What did you talk about with
Senior Min Jae on the rooftop?
What was that just now?
Ah! It's great to have a friend.
What was that kiss earlier about?
Well...
Why did you ask?
Dammit...
Min Jae's lower classman...
Surely he didn't see anything, right?
Don't tell me
he saw...
That kiss with Min Jae.
Back then...
What did you talk about with
Senior Min Jae on the rooftop?
Min Jae's favorite drink!
Min Jae... Min Jae...
Right!
So what if he sees?
Friends can do that, right?
I'll give it to Min Jae.
Hey, Yoon Chan!
Senior.
What have you been saying
by yourself since earlier?
I'll drink this.
Thanks.
Umm... Wait.
What...
I'll give it to Min Jae.
This guy...
Alright, alright.
Yoon Chan, Min Jae, cross!
The dean is here right now.
I don't have time to play with you,
hurry up and go.
Haa...
Did I chase him away too coldly?
What are you doing here?
Did you wait for me all this time?
Ah... What, we can just meet tomorrow.
Why did you wait for me until now?
Right, we can meet tomorrow.
If not, the day after.
How much have I suffered because of you?
Huh? What did you say?
Geez!
Are you a kid or what?
That hurts!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was busy today
and ended up being cold to you.
Today, I really miss you.
Yeah, I got it.
I got it, just let go for now.
Why did the dean come to the library?
Oh...
So that's why you were busy.
Today must have been tough.
Right?
Why did the dean come?
It's tough for Min Jae.
Chan.
Yeah?
One question at a time.
That way I can at least give you
some answers.
I'm just curious.
What are you so curious about?
What are you doing right now?
Are you thinking about me too?
We're not in a romantic relationship,
why are you so curious?
Hey.
Isn't that something close friends
feel for each other?
Don't you like me?
Is it...
true that I like you too?
And more importantly,
you must not move forward alone.
Most importantly, how much do
the two of you share stories
with each other?
Your confusion might be because
you still haven't broken free
from the framework set by yourself.
Or someone else's frameworks
that are unnecessary.
That could be why
you're still struggling.
Huh?
Where...
do you like me?
Where?
Your mind.
I like your mind the most.
Huh? I've always treated you
coldly though.
But you like my mind?
When I look at you,
I can see
what you really feel in your eyes.
No way.
How would you know my heart?
Your heart is beating so fast,
are you going to faint?
Do you like me that much?
Hey!
It's not like that!
Tell me why you're always
following me around!
Because when I look at you,
it's like looking at myself.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying we're similar?
Yes.
No way, that's crazy.
Even our personalities are different,
how could we be similar?
Well?
There have been times when
I've been like you too.
Because I don't always laugh every day,
and you're not always cold either.
What? What's gotten into you?
Why so serious?
What for?
You're way too serious.
Let's just go home.
Your home?
No.
You go to your dorm,
and I'll go to my place.
Okay, I'm off.
I want to visit Min Jae's place!
Go home and look in the mirror.
You and I are quite similar.
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Putting an end to the waiting,
and stealing your heart away.
Hello, it's the youngest, Woo Hyuk.
Hello, it's Min Jae.
I'm really enjoying
my time with Woo Hyuk.
Because seems a bit rough
around the edges,
but sometimes he has a cute side.
So, time flies when we're together,
and we're having fun.
Umm...
Brother Min Jae, as you can see,
is obviously cool.
He has a good personality,
and he's good at singing, right?
Geez...
- You're awesome, right?
- Come on...
But why do you like me?
Well...
Is there a reason for liking someone?
But... That guy...
What’s your relationship
with that tall guy?
We're just close friends.
Close friends that kiss?
How did you know about that?
Because I saw.
Huh? I don't think you did.
I know everything.
It's because you saw the preview.
Anyway, please look forward to
the chemistry between me and Woo Hyuk
in 'Blossom Campus',
please leave us a comment.
Yes.
Please enjoy it.
Yes! Thank you!
Please watch a lot!
Goodbye.