"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 4: Just Ordinary Friends)
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
- Stop.
- Why?
- Hey.
- What?
I said I'm hungry.
- Treat me to a meal.
- But you said that you'd treat me.
- You said you'd treat me.
- I have no money.
You said you'd treat me to
something delicious.
Senior!
Thanks for bringing the equipment.
Ah, it was nothing.
Is this the location?
No, we have to go further up.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm really glad I get to work
with you, senior.
So don't worry and use me
as much as you want.
Thank you for saying that.
Who would've thought?
We'd suddenly have to shoot
a music video.
Right?
The professor gave us assignments
without our input.
But I like it.
You're okay with anything I say.
I'm fine with it.
It's a problem if you're
okay with anything.
Ah, I'm only like this with you, senior!
Shall we go up then?
Yes.
Do we go up there?
If we carry the luggage
and walk up there, we may die.
Just take the cart.
The cart?
Yeah, the cart.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
That's pretty over there.
Ah, yes, it's pretty.
Wow, as expected of Min Jae senior.
So cool.
Woo Hyuk.
Yes, yes!
Since you're also a key staff member
in this music video,
Your interpretation should be included.
Let's make sure to record
our interpretations for each scene.
- Yes, senior.
- Okay.
Here.
Here's good too.
Oh!
Woo Hyuk.
Let's listen and see if
it suits the atmosphere here.
- Is this your song?
- Yeah.
Your confused heart,
- can I perhaps look into it
- How is it?
- with my eyes?
- Oh...
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
- A heart that drifts
- Woo Hyuk, want me to take a photo?
- with the wind...
- you'll get lots of likes on instagram.
- as if it's being swept away
- Sure.
- by the waves.
- Hold on.
Your uncertain heart,
- I want to reach out
- Woo Hyuk, one step to the right
and hold it tightly.
Pose more naturally.
Don't mind the camera.
Senior, this natural pose is
kind of difficult, isn't it?
Oh! It's good now!
If you pose naturally,
I'll take good shots.
(This morning's workout was so tough
Min Jae)
(Min Jae, what are you doing?)
(Hey...)
(Kim Min Jae)
Today was really nice.
Huh?
Ah, the music video!
I think this place is
perfect for shooting.
Right?
Look at this.
If the protagonist
walks through here,
it would be nice.
Oh!
Senior.
Are you planning to transfer to
the film department?
Hey, shooting a movie isn't easy.
Senior, hand it to me.
I'll hold onto it.
No need.
I used it, so I'll keep it.
When our professor
assigned us to make
a music video this time,
I was actually not okay
with it at first.
Do we really have to do this in
the Applied Music Department?
But
when I teamed up with you, senior,
and worked together,
I now understand why the professor
gave us a project like this.
At first, I...
was really worried about
how to shoot the music video.
But when the professor said.
That we would see the song we made
from a different perspective,
I'm starting to understand it
little by little.
And it would have been
impossible without you.
Thank you so much.
Right? You feel assured with me.
The face that senior not only
directed the music video
but also created a song,
I think it's really cool.
Oh, that's because
other teams didn't want to direct,
so I took charge.
Geez,
but ultimately, because you took charge,
it's turning out even better.
Thanks to you,
I'm learning a lot from you, senior.
I really want to worship you, you know?
What are you talking about?
I'm not God, okay?
Our relationship is equal.
Keep that in mind. Don't forget that.
Yes, I'll remember it.
The phrase "keep that in mind",
automatically creates
a hierarchical relationship.
What a guy.
But, senior,
who will be the protagonist
of the music video?
Should we ask for help from
the Acting Department?
I've already chosen.
Huh?
Already?
Wow, as expected of the senior.
Amazing determination.
I decided just now.
Just now?
You've been with me all day today.
I wanted you to do it.
Huh? Me?
Ah, senior, how can I play the lead...
That doesn't make sense, senior.
Why not?
I saw earlier that you could do it well.
You know my song the best,
you've heard it a lot,
and you can express the emotions well.
But how can I...
Don't worry, I'll be by your side.
I believe you. You believe me.
It shouldn't be a problem.
I'll try.
Don't go back on your word.
And how long are you going to
keep calling me "senior"?
Being too polite can be
a bit uncomfortable.
Call me "older brother."
Yes, older brother.
Hey, Yoon Chan!
Yes, senior.
What have you been up to lately?
Huh?
What have you been doing
that you're not paying attention
to Taekwondo?
Senior.
I've never missed a workout.
Listen,
it's not about showing up
for the workout,
it's about the result.
It was clear that you practice
for the sake of practice.
Senior,
that's a misunderstanding.
I'm really working hard.
Hey.
The guy who's working hard
is always hanging out
with that librarian?
Well, that's...
We're friends, so we hang out
after practice.
What friends...
You two were being lovey-dovey.
I don't know what you're
so preoccupied with right now,
but Taekwondo is your top priority!
Got it?
The competition is near,
and you're so preoccupied.
Yes, senior.
I'm always keeping it in mind.
But what's really going on
between you two?
Why?
Can't you tell me your relationship?
We're just friends.
Really?
Yes.
It's just a typical friendship.
Really?
Yoon Chan.
Stay focused until
the competition is over.
Yes, senior.
Min Jae!
I called you, didn't you hear me?
What's wrong, Min Jae?
What's wrong?
Tell me, I'll take care of it.
Why are you acting like this today?
You're not usually like this.
Not like me?
Yeah.
I'm just like everyone else.
What do you mean?
I'm just being normal,
like our relationship.
Yes,
it's really just a typical friendship.
Min Jae!
Min Jae! Aren't we friends?
I never promised to be your friend.
Yes, come in.
Hello, Professor.
Huh?
Min Jae's friend, Yoon Chan?
Yes, that's right.
What brings a Taekwondo major to
the Applied Music Department?
I need some counseling
from the professor.
Oh, really?
Counseling with me?
Yes.
Min Jae told me that...
The professor is
a life counseling expert, he said.
Did our Min Jae say that?
Oh, that boy.
Come on, come and have a seat.
What's troubling you
to come to a professor from
another department for counseling.
You see,
we've met a few times, right?
Feel free to open up
and share your concerns.
Professor, do you know Min Jae well?
Um... I suppose so.
What kind of person is Min Jae?
What kind of person?
You seem quite close to him,
the closer you get,
the more curious you are about Min Jae.
Min Jae, he...
Although he looks a lot like me,
his personality is completely different,
so I really can't a prediction.
Right?
You can't make a prediction?
But you know,
we don't know ourselves well enough.
How can you expect to fully
understand the other person?
Unless you're a god, how could you?
But
most human relationships are
improvised.
Actually, I'm not good at improvisation.
According to Min Jae,
aren't you the type to always improvise?
Does Min Jae talk about me a lot?
Umm...
Min Jae is also...
not good at finding friends,
like you.
So he often shares
his inner thoughts with me.
Even though my actions seem spontaneous,
I actually always plan my actions
in my own way.
Especially with Min Jae.
Do you really like Min Jae a lot?
Excuse me?
Isn't that it?
Confusion is also part of the emotions.
It seems like Min Jae is like that too.
Min Jae too?
Even so, the good thing is
the two of you go well together.
Whether as friends
or with other feelings,
when you're together,
there can be complaints
and arguments.
But through that,
your relationship becomes stronger.
Min Jae doesn't have
many friends to begin with.
Just like you.
Min Jae has many aspects that are warm,
but he had to live his life on his own.
So he has to hide
that gentleness inside,
and became cold on the outside.
Um...
In a way,
having friends might have seemed
like a luxury for him.
So having someone like me around
could have been burdensome for Min Jae.
Um...
At first, maybe.
But
since he started meeting you,
Min Jae himself
started to take off that cold mask
all by himself.
Autumn has already passed.
What is Min Jae doing now?
Should I apologize first?
Will Min Jae no longer be angry?
But does Min Jae truly
understand my feelings?
I'm the only one boiling inside.
No, no.
Still, I should apologize first.
Who is it?
It's Woo Hyuk.
I need to consult with the professor.
Hey.
Am I an applied music professor
or a philosophy professor?
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Putting an end to the waiting,
and stealing your heart away.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Yoon Chan!
A college student who loves Taekwondo.
Let's fall into the charms of Taekwondo
and someone full of laughter and energy,
someone like me.
Of course,
I'll show you plenty of my clumsy side
and my smile too.
I'll show you everything I've got
so you can all smile.
Look forward to it!