It's a relief that he's gone, but
why does he keep popping into my head?
Get a grip, Kim Min Jae.
Dammit...
This doesn't feel right.
Who the heck is that guy anyway?
I think I got swayed by his eloquence.
Do you want to be friends?
In any case, he should've contacted me.
"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 5: I'm Sorry and Thank You)
No, no.
Seriously.
I have to teach you everything
from scratch.
Yeah. This is better.
- Is this right?
- Yeah.
Good job.
Oh, this is good.
Good, right?
I'm hungry.
What should we eat?
What do you want to eat?
Min Jae.
I have something to say.
Woo Hyuk, go ahead first.
Yes, senior.
I'll wait in the club room.
You said you had something to say.
Min Jae, I'm sorry.
I know why you're upset, but
I just said that to the senior
to make an excuse.
So?
Is that a reason to treat me like this?
I just said it without thinking.
I was just expressing my thoughts.
So, don't worry about it.
How can I not worry
when you make that face?
Why do you care?
I'm just an ordinary friend
of yours, right?
No, I said that's not what I meant.
Just because you said no
and it'll be fine?
Those words you said so easily
without any concern.
Anyway...
I realized your thoughts are
very different from mine.
Of course, thoughts are different.
Isn't the point to adjust to
each other's differences?
Anyway...
Can't you just let this go?
Fine.
Just leave me and go as you said.
Then it'll be over.
Hey, Kim Min Jae!
Yoon Chan, why did you...
Not like this...
Am I being too narrow-minded?
(Yoon Chan)
Hello?
Min Jae.
- It's me.
- Yeah, I know.
Are you very sick?
What?
How did you know?
You haven't been at university
for two days.
I asked the professor.
Why? Did you think I died or something?
What are you saying?
I came because I was worried.
Huh?
You came?
Where?
In front of your house.
Who told you to come? Just go away!
Hey, Kim Min Jae.
Isn't this too much?
I even came all the way to your house.
And you tell me to go?
Damn it...
Look,
my condition is terrible right now,
can we talk here and then you leave?
First, take this.
Hey!
You're full of revenge aren't you?
Huh?
What?
I'm going to watch you finish
that bowl of porridge and I'll leave.
Fine.
So this is Kim Min Jae's place.
You've kept it pretty tidy.
Hey,
did you think I wouldn't keep it clean?
Right. Because you're Mr. Clean,
Kim Min Jae.
But right now it's a bit...
Messy?
It's because I've been sick
for two days.
I know, I know.
That's why I'm here.
Eat it before it gets cold.
What is it now?
Do you want me to feed you?
No, thanks.
It's creepy.
See, I told you I'd feed you.
Aah...
Hey, why are you eating my porridge?
I just took a bite to see
if it was good.
Geez.
No need, I'll eat it all myself.
You bought it after all.
Wow, you eat well!
See, you need me.
I'm eating it because you went through
the trouble of buying it.
See, you're still not fully recovered.
- I'm sorry.
And
thank you
for having the courage to come.
Who's there?
It's Woo Hyuk, senior.
Senior, I brought some porridge,
please have some.
Min Jae!
You're full, right?
He has already eaten
the porridge I bought.
Sorry.
I already ate the porridge Chan bought.
But thanks for bringing it.
I'll put it in the fridge
and eat it later.
Okay.
Should I put it in the fridge now?
I bought it,
so I'll put it away.
- Chan.
- Yeah?
Aren't you hungry?
I had some of your porridge earlier.
Hyuk, Hyuk,
aren't you hungry?
Shall we eat some porridge then?
See, you are hungry.
Yeah, a little.
Hey, you didn't act like this with me.
But in front of the senior,
you act all cutesy.
What did I do?
It's strange, really.
It's like you're discriminating.
What?
Why would I act cute with you?
See?
So, you were acting cute
in front of the senior!
Senior,
don't you find this strange?
It's really weird.
Why can't you just act normal?
Why do you turn into a baby
in front of Senior?
Because I like him!
Min... Min Jae.
I'm going to head out first.
I shouldn't be too late for the dorm.
Already?
Yeah, okay.
Hey, senior,
I like you a lot too,
but I don't act all cutesy
in front of you.
I don't think things
should turn out like this.
Yoon Chan.
Why did you come out when
you're still not feeling well?
Yoon Chan.
Yeah?
I...
feel anxious.
Why?
Because I don't know whether
it's okay to like you.
Why does that make you anxious
when I like you?
Because...
whenever I like someone,
they always leave.
Whenever I like someone,
something always happens
that makes them leave.
Min Jae.
I won't be like that.
Even if something happens,
I won't leave.
I feel so good when I see you,
my heart feels that way,
but my head gets all confused.
I've always been...
bad luck for the other person.
Min Jae.
I'm closer to being bad luck incarnate
instead of good fortune.
Let's gather our bad luck together
and instead of seeking luck,
let's create some happiness.
You trust me, right?
Min Jae.
You just need to choose.
Is it Woo Hyuk
or me?
Geez,
you're joking in this situation.
It's you, of course.
My Min Jae cried and then laughed,
you look even cuter.
Oh, you need to go back to the dorm.
Min Jae.
Yeah?
Kiss.
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Hello, I'm Min Jae.
And here is Yoon Chan,
who loves Taekwondo.
Yes, every moment with
Yoon Chan is so enjoyable.
My Yoon Chan is tall,
handsome, and dependable.
If there's one downside,
it's that he's a bit clumsy.
But that's my charm.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, that's right.
As for my Min Jae,
I'm happy with just being with him.
If you ask me why,
it's because of his music,
his gaze, his touch...
He's so warm.
And he's good-looking.
And he's so cold.
But still,
I like Min Jae.
I'm not cold.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
To Yoon Chan, I'm warm.
- You're warm? Really?
- Yes, of course.
Oh...
Please love Min Jae and Yoon Chan
of 'Blossom Campus' a lot.
Let's see each other often.
- See you often. Bye-bye.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.