I feel so good when I see you,
my heart feels that way,
but my head gets all confused.
I've always been...
bad luck for the other person.
Min Jae.
I'm closer to being bad luck incarnate
than good fortune.
Let's gather our bad luck together
and instead of seeking luck,
let's create some happiness.
You just need to choose.
Is it Woo Hyuk
or me?
Geez,
you're joking in this situation.
It's you, of course.
My Min Jae cried and then laughed,
you look even cuter.
Min Jae.
Yeah?
Let's kiss.
"Blossom Campus"
(Chapter 6: So, what are we?)
- Have you worked at a café before?
- Yes.
I worked at one for about a year
when I was a freshman.
Ah, and thank you.
- For remembering and reaching out.
- You're welcome.
You seemed really desperate back then,
so I remembered you well.
And for such a good looking person
to come back,
I'm even more grateful.
So, you can make coffee...
Excellent.
Yes, you only need to
teach me how to bake cakes.
Well, Mr. Min Jae's appearance
is so great,
that might sell better than cakes.
However,
On weekdays, you have to study
and work at your university,
and our shop is very busy.
Can you handle it?
That's okay.
I'm confident in my stamina.
Oh, great. So then,
you'll start working starting from
the upcoming weekend.
- Yes, boss.
- See you then.
Yes! Thank you!
Good morning!
Huh? Chan!
Thanks for coming.
Actually,
I was a bit scared to
open the shop alone.
Ah, stop exaggerating.
You got it done in the end.
But aren't you glad I came?
Of course, I am.
Just having you by my side
makes me feel so secure.
Order anything you want,
I'll help with everything.
Yeah.
You know I'm really grateful, right?
Come here.
The cake here is really delicious.
Chan!
You didn't eat breakfast, did you?
I saved a piece of cake for you.
Let's eat together.
I don't like sweet stuff.
Even this?
- Let's get to work.
- Sure.
I've decided,
but can I add a shot of liquor?
I don't think that's a good idea.
But I think it's fine.
But our shop doesn't
offer extra shots of liquor.
One cup, right?
Can I have a long black with
a cinnamon stick and apple juice?
That's this one.
It's just hot water added to it.
Ah.
Yoon Chan, this is my heart.
Here, eat.
No.
This is also my heart.
It's cute.
Don't put it there.
Put it back on.
Okay.
Enjoy your meal.
Yeah.
Serve them well.
Who ordered the latte?
Enjoy your drink.
Today was tough, huh?
It's very different from
when I am a customer.
Right?
There's more to working at a
cafépart time than you think.
You have to work in the café,
and serve the customers.
I've always played sports,
so my stamina supported me.
Being a librarian and
a weekend part-timer,
it's amazing how you don't collapse.
I get tired too.
But.
After living a difficult life
all this time, your endurance builds up.
I'm not too far behind you in stamina.
You've been through a lot.
Mr. Kim Min Jae.
I should probably catch up
on the dishes now.
You should take a break,
Mr. Kim Min Jae.
I'll do the dishes.
Sir, it's time to wake up,
Mr. Kim Min Jae.
Does my coffee taste better?
Shouldn't you be the one
working at the café?
Have you finished the dishes?
Of course. Who am I covering for?
I made sure to do everything perfectly
so you wouldn't get in trouble.
Then...
shall I go check whether
I'll get fired or not?
I already managed it, how was it?
Umm...
- Thanks.
- Really?
Did I do well?
You did great!
You did great too.
I have to hurry up and
make a lot of money,
so Min Jae will be more comfortable.
You can't even tie a ribbon properly.
Min Jae, did you know?
Your ribbon is a mess too!
Huh?
Turn around, I'll do it for you.
- Boss!
- Mmm.
Did you finish your business?
Yeah, I did. Who is this?
He's my best friend, Yoon Chan.
Ah, so this is your friend.
Nice to meet you.
- Hello, I'm Yoon Chan.
- Yes.
Wow, impressive.
Yoon Chan helped me a lot today.
Oh, I see.
Thank you so much.
Was it tough?
Oh, working at a café sure isn't easy.
But
it was fun working with Min Jae.
If you're okay with it...
how about working at the café too?
Together with Min Jae?
Sure, well, I'll get busier with work.
I was planning to hire
one more part-timer.
It'd be nice if we could work together.
That's a yes, right?
- Sure.
- Okay, you're so tall.
Very tall.
- I'm glad.
- Yeah.
Huh? What's this?
Ah.
Ham for the Budae jjigae.
- Ham?
- Yeah.
This is just regular sausage.
Oh, is it?
Can't it go in the Budae jjigae?
I like this sausage.
Everything you make tastes good.
But I'll dip this sausage in egg
and fry it for you.
What about the ham?
A Budae jjigae without ham is like
Kim Min Jae without Yoon Chan.
I'll go quickly and get some.
No, no.
I'll go and get it. You finish it, yeah?
Okay.
What's this?
Why did you follow me?
Because I was worried.
That you might use ham as an excuse
and go meet someone else.
Hey,
don't you dare.
Stop it.
- Stop it.
- No.
Stop it.
Wait for me!
Why are you here?
Your confused heart,
can I perhaps look into it with my eyes?
If you allow me for a moment,
I'll embrace you with my two arms.
A heart that drifts with the wind,
as if it's being swept away by the waves.
Your uncertain heart,
I want to reach out and hold it tightly.
Putting an end to the waiting,
and stealing your heart away.
Without a word,
I shall take everything of yours
I'm almost going crazy
I can no longer stay still
I shall be the first to take leave.
Stepping forth to enfold your heart,
Dancing through the highs and lows tonight.
Hello, everyone!
I'm Kim Min Jae.
Shall we dive together into
the world of applied music?
The story of music and love,
and my determination.
I want everyone to watch it together.
Please give lots of love to
our show 'Blossom Campus',
And please love me, Min Jae, too.
Now then, goodbye.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Hello, everyone.
Nice to meet you.
Isn't it time for Min Jae to come?
Ding-dong.
Chan!
Sorry for being late.
My part-time job ended late.
You worked hard today too, Min Jae.
I made a lot of money today.
Shall we properly greet
our audience again?
- Sure.
- Hello.
I'm actor Son Byeong Hoon,
who plays Min Jae in 'Blossom Campus.'
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm actor Choi Dong Ho,
who plays Yoon Chan.
How do you feel?
Honestly, before starting,
I thought, "Oh, it'll be okay."
"I'll do well." That's what I thought.
But now that I'm actually doing it,
I'm a bit nervous,
And it seems like I might make mistakes.
What did you do?
Just before I came here.
- You shouldn't have.
- My pronunciation got a bit messed up.
Ah, I see.
What about Min Jae?
Since I'm meeting new people,
I'm feeling very excited and happy.
You two match so well.
Do we?
Let's see for ourselves.
What was your motivation for
participating in 'Blossom Campus'?
I wanted to challenge myself in
a genre I've always wanted to try.
I had only played student roles before,
But this time, I got to play
the lead character for the first time.
As for me, I didn't have
any acting experience at all.
So when I first passed the audition,
it was amazing.
But I was very worried.
I was worried if I could do well.
You did well.
I thought, "There must be a reason
for being chosen,"
I decided to do my best.
So, I accepted it.
Did you imagine what BL series shooting
would be like before shooting?
Was there anything that surprised you
during BL shooting?
There wasn't anything
particularly surprising,
I had some idea of what
it'd be like beforehand.
It was really fun.
But one thing shocked me,
there's a scene where we were
doing a plane pose,
I was shocked by that.
I was a bit surprised by a scene,
it was originally a pecking scene,
but suddenly Yoon Chan
got really into it
and kissed me.
I was surprised then.
Since the camera was already rolling,
So it became a kissing scene.
- It's a behind-the-scene.
- A behind-the-scene.
Did you become close right away
during your first shoot?
Yes, we slept together right away
during our first shoot.
Yes, we slept in the same room,
we had no choice but to become close.
Before then, we weren't very close,
but after our first shoot,
We slept together in the same room,
so we talked a lot.
I think we became much closer then.
What is your favorite characteristic of
your fellow actor's character?
First, the face.
It's not a characteristic,
I like his face,
it's kind of tsundere.
I felt like he treated me well,
so I really liked that characteristic.
Thank you.
For me, it's Yoon Chan's physique.
Yoon Chan works out really hard,
so his body is really good.
How did you create chemistry
between you two?
Before shooting,
we joked around a lot
and played around a lot.
We also met outside separately
and had a lot of fun.
- That's right.
- We wanted to capture that feeling
during the shoot,
we tried to focus on loving each other.
So we kept meeting,
drinking together,
- and hanging out together.
- Right.
We went to Yoon Chan's house
together to sleep.
And then to my house to sleep.
How much do you empathize with
the characters in "Blossom Campus"?
I empathized and expressed
Min Jae's character's sad side.
Min Jae is really determined.
He leads a life of hardship.
He tries really hard to protect himself,
I felt like Yoon Chan's character is
tough on the outside, but he's a softie,
and he has no friends.
But when he talked to
Min Jae the first time,
he was really happy.
I don't know how to approach others,
so when someone approaches me first,
I get really happy.
I could relate to that a lot.
The charm of
the other person's character?
Well, Yoon Chan's character
looks really cool and tall
on the outside,
but inside, he feels like a nerd.
Because he doesn't have many friends.
But I found that really charming.
At first, I thought Min Jae
was just a pretty face and a stuck-up.
But as we got closer,
I realized it wasn't just that,
I found his personality really charming.
Min Jae...
Honestly,
he's not really that kind.
I mean, he's probably just
trying to protect himself,
since he has his own circumstances
and stuff, you know?
It seems to be a charm that is
only given to people he likes.
He's cold to others,
he only shows that side to Yoon Chan,
I found that really attractive.
The charm of Yoon Chan's character is
he only focuses on one person.
That's so attractive to me.
I like someone who likes only me.
Right.
Was it hard to portray the characters?
Or were you inspired
by other actors?
At first, it was really difficult.
Yoon Chan's character
transitions from being cold
to being really cheerful, right?
I didn't feel like I was
naturally that cheerful,
So I really thought
a lot about that part.
I studied "Choco Milk Shake" for that.
I watched it and thought,
"Maybe I should do it like this."
It should be helpful.
I think I pondered that a lot.
It was difficult to portray Min Jae...
Rather,
there were a lot of ambiguous aspects.
I tried to draw inspiration from
many characters in different works.
The work that inspired me the most was
"Semantic Error".
"Semantic Error," oh.
What's your favorite scene from it?
Please describe it briefly.
Tell us your favorite scene
in five characters.
"Café apron."
Does that make sense?
It's too suggestive.
Just now, it popped back into my head.
The cooking scene.
I really like that scene.
That scene was very sweet.
Did you ever feel fluttery
with another party while filming?
For me, it's the rooftop scene.
- The rooftop?
- Yes.
- The university rooftop?
For me, it's that scene,
when Min Jae took me to his house.
The character has
a self-defense instinct, right?
But letting me into his house,
the barrier breaks down
and he accepts me.
Isn't it just your own thoughts?
Is it?
I felt excited about that part.
If "Blossom Campus" continues
with another season,
would you appear again?
If Min Jae is in, then I'm in.
You won't do it if I'm not in?
Right.
Me too.
We've answered all the questions,
how does everyone feel?
We're really grateful for
the many questions.
Being able to talk with fans
even in this formal setting
is really wonderful.
- Right.
- And Min Jae?
This is the first time I'm filmed
with multiple cameras like this,
so it's really fascinating.
It's really fun,
but it's too bad, time flies so fast.
Right.
Even though it's been such
a short time today,
thank you for watching.
Thank you, everyone.
We're not sure if our Q&A was helpful,
but we hope it was.
Please love 'Blossom Campus, ' everyone.
If we get another chance,
I hope we can do this again.
It's not 'if we get' another chance,
it's 'we must.'
We'll meet again.
We'll just declare it
and the CEO will
inevitably provide it.
- We'll see you again!
- Let's meet again.
- We'll return!
- Goodbye!
We'll come again, everyone.
Goodbye, thank you for watching.